https://www.safelaneglobal.com/en/privacy/

Privacy policy
1) What does this policy cover?
This privacy policy applies only to your use of this website.  This site may contain links to other websites.  Please note that SafeLane Global has no control over how your data is collected, stored or used by other websites and  advises you to check the privacy policies of any such websites before providing any data to them.
2) Your rights
As a data subject, you have the following rights under the UK’s data protection legislation, which this policy and SafeLane Global’s use of personal data have been designed to uphold:
The right to be informed about SafeLane Global’s collection and use of personal data;
The right of access to the personal data SafeLane Global holds about you;
The right to rectification if any personal data it holds about you is inaccurate or incomplete (please contact SafeLane Global using the details below);
The right to be forgotten – i.e. the right to ask SafeLane Global to delete any personal data it holds about you (it only holds your personal data for a limited time, as explained below but if you would like it to delete it sooner, please contact SafeLane Global using the details below);
The right to restrict (i.e. prevent) the processing of your personal data;
The right to data portability (obtaining a copy of your personal data to re-use with another service or organisation);
The right to object to SafeLane Global using your personal data for particular purposes; and
Rights with respect to automated decision making and profiling.
If you have any cause for complaint about SafeLane Global’s use of your personal data, please contact the company using the details provided in section 12 and it will do its best to solve the problem for you.  If it is unable to help, you also have the right to lodge a complaint with the UK’s supervisory authority, the Information Commissioner’s Office.
For further information about your rights, please contact the Information Commissioner’s Office or your local Citizens Advice Bureau.
3) What data does SafeLane Global collect?
Depending upon your use of SafeLane Global’s site, it may collect some or all of the following personal [and non-personal] data (please also see the section below on use of cookies and similar technologies:
[name;]
[business/company name]
[contact information such as email addresses and telephone numbers;]
[IP address;]
[web browser type and version;]
[operating system;]
[a list of URLs starting with a referring site, your activity on this site, and the site you exit to;]
4) How does SafeLane Global use your data?
All personal data is processed and stored securely, for no longer than is necessary in light of the reason(s) for which it was first collected.  SafeLane Global will comply with its obligations and safeguard your rights under the UK’s data protection legislation at all times.  For more details on security see below.
SafeLane Global’s use of your personal data will always have a lawful basis, either because it is necessary for its performance of a contract with you, because you have consented to its use of your personal data (e.g. by subscribing to the SafeLane Global newsletter), or because it is in SafeLane Global’s legitimate interests.  Specifically, SafeLane Global may use your data for the following purposes:
[Providing and managing your access to the site;]
[Personalising and tailoring your experience on the site;]
[Replying to emails or queries from you;]
[Supplying you with emails that you have opted in to (you may unsubscribe or opt-out at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link in the footer of any emails SafeLane Global sends you;]
[Analysing your use of  the site [and gathering feedback] to enable SafeLane Global to continually improve its site and your user experience;]
With your permission and/or where permitted by law, SafeLane Global may also use your data for marketing purposes which may include contacting you by [email] AND/OR [telephone] AND/OR [text message] AND/OR [post] with information, news and offers on its [services].  It will not, however, send you any unsolicited marketing or spam and will take all reasonable steps to ensure that it fully protects your rights and complies with its obligations under the UK’s data protection legislation and the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003.
You have the right to withdraw your consent to SafeLane Global using your personal data at any time, and to request that SafeLane Global deletes it.
It does not keep your personal data for any longer than is necessary in light of the reason(s) for which it was first collected. Data will therefore be retained for the following periods (or its retention will be determined on the following bases):
IP Address, geographical and non-personally identifiable data is stored for a maximum of 2 years.
5) How and where does SafeLane Global store your data?
It only keeps your personal data for as long as it needs to in order to use it as described above, and/or for as long as it has your permission to keep it.
[Some or all of your data may be stored outside of the European Economic Area (“the EEA”) (The EEA consists of all EU member states, plus Norway, Iceland, and Liechtenstein).  You are deemed to accept and agree to this by using the site and submitting information to SafeLane Global.  If it does store data outside the EEA, it will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your data is treated as safely and securely as it would be within the UK and under the [Data Protection Act 1998]
Data security is very important to SafeLane Global, and to protect your data it has taken suitable measures to safeguard and secure data collected through this site.
Steps SafeLane Global takes to secure and protect your data include:
All non-personally identifiable data is stored with Google and is collected in cookies outlined below.
SafeLane Global may sometimes use third party data processors that are located outside of the European Economic Area (“the EEA”) (The EEA consists of all EU member states, plus Norway, Iceland, and Liechtenstein).  Where it transfers any personal data outside the EEA, it will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your data is treated as safely and securely as it would be within the UK and under the UK’s data protection legislation:
All personal data is collected and stored by MailChimp (operated by The Rocket Science Group LLC), that provides mailing services to SafeLane Global so that it can send email communications to you.  MailChimp’s servers are located in the United States [and in other countries outside the EEA].  Mailchimp provides high levels of data protection outlined here: https://mailchimp.com/about/security/ .
6) Does SafeLane Global share your data?
SafeLane Global will not share any of your data with any third parties for any purposes other than outlined in Section 5.
It may compile statistics about the use of its site including data on traffic, usage patterns, user numbers, and other information. All such data will be anonymised and will not include any personally identifying data, or any anonymised data that can be combined with other data and used to identify you.  It may from time to time share such data with third parties such as prospective investors, affiliates and partners.  Data will only be shared and used within the bounds of the law.
SafeLane Global may sometimes use third party data processors that are located outside of the European Economic Area (“the EEA”) (The EEA consists of all EU member states, plus Norway, Iceland, and Liechtenstein).  Where it transfers any personal data outside the EEA, it will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your data is treated as safely and securely as it would be within the UK and under the UK’s data protection legislation:
7) What happens if the business changes hands?
SafeLane Global may, from time to time, expand or reduce its business and this may involve the sale and/or the transfer of control of all or part of the business.  Any personal data that you have provided will, where it is relevant to any part of the business that is being transferred, be transferred along with that part and the new owner or newly controlling party will, under the terms of this privacy policy, be permitted to use that data only for the same purposes for which it was originally collected by Us.
In the event that any of your data is to be transferred in such a manner, you will [not] be contacted in advance and informed of the changes.  [When contacted you will [not, however,] be given the choice to have your data deleted or withheld from the new owner or controller.]
8) How can you control your data?
You may  wish to sign up to one or more of the preference services operating in the UK: The Telephone Preference Service (“the TPS”), the Corporate Telephone Preference Service (“the CTPS”), and the Mailing Preference Service (“the MPS”). These may help to prevent you receiving unsolicited marketing.  Please note, however, that these services will not prevent you from receiving marketing communications that you have consented to receiving.
9) Your right to withhold information
You may access certain areas of the site without providing any data at all.  However, to use all features and functions available on the site you may be required to submit or allow for the collection of certain data.
You may restrict the use of cookies.  For more information, see below.
10) How can you access your data?
Under the UK’s data protection legislation, no fee is payable and SafeLane Global will provide any and all information in response to your request free of charge.  Please contact SafeLane Global for more details at info@safelaneglobal.com or using the contact details below.
11) SafeLane Global’s use of cookies
SafeLane Global’s site may place and access certain first party cookies on your computer or device.  First party cookies are those placed directly by SafeLane Global and are used only by SafeLane Global.  It uses cookies to facilitate and improve your experience of the site and to provide and improve its services.  SafeLane Global has carefully chosen these cookies and has taken steps to ensure that your privacy and personal data is protected and respected at all times.
All cookies used by and on SafeLane Global’s site are used in accordance with current cookie law.
Before cookies are placed on your computer or device, you will be shown a **SafeLane Global cookie notice** requesting your consent to set those cookies.  By giving your consent to the placing of cookies you are enabling SafeLane Global to provide the best possible experience and service to you.  You may, if you wish, deny consent to the placing of cookies; however certain features of the site may not function fully or as intended.
Certain features depend on cookies to function.  Cookie law deems these cookies to be “strictly necessary”.  SafeLane Global has taken great care to ensure that your privacy is not at risk by allowing them.
This site uses analytics services provided by Google.  Website analytics refers to a set of tools used to collect and analyse anonymous usage information, enabling SafeLane Global to better understand how the site is used.  This, in turn, enables SafeLane Global to improve the site and the services offered through it.  You do not have to allow SafeLane Global to use these cookies, however whilst its use of them does not pose any risk to your privacy or your safe use of the site, it does enable SafeLane Global to continually improve the site, making it a better and more useful experience for you.
With respect to the Google Analytics cookies, please note that SafeLane Global has entered into a data processing agreement with Google that ensures that the last octet of your IP address is masked when SafeLane Global provides information to Google, that it does not use any other Google services in combination with Google Analytics cookies and that it does not share any data with Google for advertisement purposes.  To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
HubSpot Analytics (HubSpot, Inc.)
HubSpot Analytics is an analytics service provided by HubSpot, Inc.
Personal Data collected: Cookies; Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy – Opt Out .
Hotjar Analytics
We use Hotjar.  Hotjar is a technology service that helps us better understand our users’ experience (e.g. how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click, what users do and don’t like, etc.) and this enables us to build and maintain our service with user feedback.  Hotjar uses cookies and other technologies to collect data on our users’ behaviour and their devices.  This includes a device’s IP address (processed during your session and stored in a de-identified form), device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), and the preferred language used to display our website.  Hotjar stores this information on our behalf in a pseudonymized user profile.  Hotjar is contractually forbidden to sell any of the data collected on our behalf.
For further details, please see the ‘about Hotjar’ section of Hotjar’s support site.”
Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings.  To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.
12) Contacting SafeLane Global
If you have any questions about this site or this privacy policy, please contact SafeLane Global by email at info@safelaneglobal.com.  Please ensure that your query is clear, particularly if it is a request for information about the data  SafeLane Global holds about you.
13) Changes to this privacy policy
SafeLane Global may change this privacy policy from time to time (for example, if the law changes).  Any changes will be immediately posted on the site and you will be deemed to have accepted the terms of the privacy policy on your first use of the site following the alterations.  SafeLane Global recommends that you check this page regularly to keep up-to-date.
